

CONTACT

CARLOS ARMANDO LOPEZ ESPINOZA

(686) 283 0024

CALOPEZ9616@GMAIL.COM

MEXICALI, BAJA CALIFORNIA, MÉXICO

ABILITIES

HTML + CSS + BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT + JQUERY

ASP .NET CORE 3.1, .NET 5, .NET 6 + C#

PHP

GITHUB

SQL

LANGUAGE

SPANISH

ENGLISH

CARLOS LÓPEZ WEB DEVELOPER











ABOUT ME

WEB DEVELOPER WITH 3 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT, 1 YEAR 8 MONTHS WAS A PROFESSIONAL WAY DOING TECHNOLOGICAL SOLUTIONS FROM REQUIREMENTS OF EACH COMPANY THAT I WORKED AND APPLYING THE BEST PRACTICES OF SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT WITH ARCHITECTURES THAT LET ME MAKE A SCALABLE SYSTEM.

EDUCATION

2016-2019

LICENCIADO EN SISTEMAS COMPUTACIONALES UNIVERSIDAD AUTONÓMA DE BAJA CALIFORNIA UNIVERSITY, MEXICALI, B.C.

2012-2015

COBACH PLANTEL MAESTRO JOSÉ VASCONCELOS CALDERÓN HIGH SCHOOL MEXICALI, B.C.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2019 - NOW

BRANIX

DEVELOPER MEXICALI, B.C.

2 YEAR 4 MONTHS

OCTOBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

FREELANCER

WEB DEVELOPER MEXICALI, B.C. 1 YEAR 4 MONTHS

MORE ABILITIES

- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- INTERNET INFORMATION SERVICES(IIS)
- ELECTRONIC BILLING(SAT 4.0 AND QUICKBOOKS)
- VISUAL STUDIO 2019
- VISUAL STUDIO CODE
- SQL MANAGEMENT STUDIO





/CLOPEZ.ESPINOZA16

/CLOPEZ-ESPINOZA16